<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning on Software Developer</title>
    <link>/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learning on Software Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 09:20:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why End-to-End Testing is Important for Your Team</title>
      <link>/blog/2017-12-16-end-end-testing-important-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017-12-16-end-end-testing-important-team/</guid>
      <description>How our team did it in 4 easy steps Originally published at https://medium.freecodecamp.org/why-end-to-end-testing-is-important-for-your-team-cb7eb0ec1504
At Hubba, our business needs are always evolving and the development speed needs to catch up with it. One of the ways to keep the team moving forward without breaking everything is End-to-end Testing (E2E). Having a full test suite with E2E tests allows us to move quickly. It allows developers to push code without the worry of breaking things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning a New Technology</title>
      <link>/blog/2014-04-01-learning-new-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 08:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2014-04-01-learning-new-technology/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s tough learning a new technology because you have no idea where to start, so you end up procrastinating and saying that you will learn it later or &amp;#8220;tomorrow&amp;#8221; and then it never happens. This still happens to me, but I have found a solution! The best way to learn a new library or framework is to use it on an existing project or use it on a new project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internship - A Learning Experience</title>
      <link>/blog/2013-10-20-internship-learning-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 12:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2013-10-20-internship-learning-experience/</guid>
      <description>I had just recently completed my 8 week internship as a Web Developer. It was an amazing learning experience so I figure why not write about it.
The Job Search After graduating, I felt that my skills were &amp;#8216;good enough&amp;#8217; to seek a full-time or contract job. I was applying for jobs for about a month, I got a couple of interviews/coding tests and one company really boosted my morale by saying only 10% pass their coding test (still skeptical but positivity was what I needed at that point).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>